let's look at the solution to our cash
summary quiz we already know that the
least significant 5 bits are the offset
bits that there are eight blocks in this
cache and because it's 2-way
set-associative that means that the next
two bits are the index bits so all of
these have the same index bits which
means they map to the same cache set so
we only really need to consider what
happens in the one set where they go
this is a load it's gonna be a miss
because the cache is empty so we have a
Miss now the valid dirty and tag bits in
the set are gonna be 1 here and 0 here
dirty is 0 and the tag is b c d e 0 0
it's actually gonna have slightly more
bits but this is the only part that will
really differ between these the next
access is c d e f it's gonna be a mess
and we'll fetch it into the other entry
here the dirty bit is 0 because this is
a load next we have a store hit because
we are accessing this it's a hit because
it's a store this becomes dirty next we
have a store to another world in the
same block so this block becomes dirty
and then we have a store again to BCD so
it's just a hit that sets this dirty bit
again to 1 so overall we had two misses
and 0 right backs in this sequence